With her undeserved death, Asalem v. Seleucia, loyal subject and beloved member of the royal family, has revealed the truth to us.
Through her sacrifice, she has opened our eyes.
We seek justice. Earth has spat upon our good faith, heaped us with insult, and has committed this unspeakable atrocity.
And now, retribution is at hand because this day, we declare war against planet Earth!
Block 63B, clear! Block 63C, clear! There's no sign he's escaped from the castle! Track him down, now! Yes, sir!
Damn Terran. How could he use the audience chamber like that? I want him shot on sight!
Lord Cruteo, hold that thought a moment.
What is it, Lord Sosbo?
This boy is the son of Dr. Troyard. I believe we should question him more about his father's Alt-Noah research.
Could I trouble you to take him alive?
Continue. Tell me what happened after that.
And the orange cataphract. I need you to tell me more about it.
この悩南競陵 giveramination物か?
It does not come to me.
I need you to tell your story.
It is time for any invitation.
It is time for your future with goodoine.
Thank you.
Attention, everyone! Assembly in the briefing room right now!
Hey, Yuki, what's going on?
Warrant Officer Kaisuka, please.
As of this moment, we're officially at war with them, too.
As of right now, you are all drafted into military service, subject to military regulations.
You are obligated to perform the duties of which you are assigned.
I look forward to seeing what you can do.
You're young. It's unfair.
But now you are warriors, and it's your job to safeguard the peace and safety of Earth.
This ship will resupply and put in for needed repairs at Tanigashima base.
Thereafter, we will likely go to UFE HQ in Russia.
All right, everyone. Please go to your assigned duty stations.
That is all. You are dismissed.
I'm Soma Yagarai, age 28. Specialties are surgery and behavioral medicine.
My door is always open if you ever need any counseling.
Thank you for your help, Doctor.
You see? My big sister has been too sick to go to school for a long time now.
Oh, is that so?
Isn't that right, Your Highness?
Uh, yes.
That's why Her Highness has never received any military training, because she's far too frail to be a soldier.
Oh.
However, as for myself, I can pilot a cataphract.
Well, when you're all grown up, please do, okay?
I will. Bye.
One more thing. Why do you call your sister Your Highness?
Because to me, my big sister is my beloved princess.
Please forgive my behavior, milady.
That's quite all right, and I thank you.
And what about you?
How old are you, please?
Everyone who had military training in high school is being drafted.
Well, I was kept out of school. For family reasons.
I see.
Well, there are plenty of things you can help with, even if you're not fighting.
You can still support everyone else who did get military training in school.
I'm sure you want to do your part to defend Earth against the Martians.
All right, McKay, we're clear.
Let's just back it up.
Why was I made a maintenance worker instead of a pilot?
You think it's because you flunked out of piloting?
Hey, mechanics are really crucial.
Without them, all the cataphracts would fall apart on us.
How am I supposed to waste any Martians stuck here in the hangar?
Hey, don't be so gung-ho.
These past 15 years, nobody's seen any real action out there.
Because all those who did are dead now.
That goes for the Martians, too.
Meaning that everybody, friend or foe, is a virgin to this, just like you.
Well, not everybody.
Inaho, you mean, are you saying that...
You lived through it, didn't you, Lieutenant?
And you're still alive.
Oh, that's what you're talking about.
Let's just say opinions are divided.
The Tanigashima report I wrote was buried really deep.
Tanigashima report is what?
That's the place where the first fragments came to Earth when the moon was destroyed 15 years ago during Heaven's Fall.
Yeah.
But something else came down well before the moon did.
Soldiers for the Empire.
We went up against those monstrous Martian cataphracts and dilapidated tanks that were obsolete.
They wiped us out.
Then the Hypergate went out of control and turned the moon into Heaven's Fall.
And the Martians wiped the battlefield clean.
But there's no physical evidence.
My report was deemed the ramblings of a madman written in terror.
But how could they?
It was the truth.
Mars' cataphracts are way beyond what Earth's technology can produce.
Either way, it'll be the same result.
Because Earth doesn't have Alt-Noah Drives.
Alt-Noah Drives.
Fugitive located.
He's in the Sky Carrier hangar.
Do not let him get away.
How long will he continue making me look like a fool?
The basics are the same as the training units.
Even with the higher output, if gravity and surface hardness don't change, agility will only decrease to the extent that its weight increases.
I'll just have to acclimate.
So this is where you've been?
All by yourself?
Yes.
This is beautiful.
Truly.
Is a blue sky that unusual to you?
Yes.
Are you studying something?
Just brushing up a little.
Don't know if it'll be very useful, though.
Oh, really?
Why not?
Because here on Earth, we don't have Alt-Noah.
Huh.
What is it anyway, Alt-Noah?
Alt-Noah is a kind of technology from a civilization that was discovered in ancient ruins on Verse.
Our world that you call Mars.
The first human to ever make contact and awaken it was Dr. Ray Regalia Verse Rayverse.
He is my grandfather and the Emperor of Verse.
And when it once again activated after so many eons, Alt-Noah saw Grandfather as its rightful heir, and branded his very genes with the Alt-Noah activation factor.
So then that means...
Yes, the only ones with the innate ability to use the power of Alt-Noah are Grandfather and his descendants.
In exchange for the knights swearing allegiance to him, he gave them the gift of Alt-Noah and its activation factor.
Using that power, the knights created mighty castles and cataphracts and ruled over the colonies.
Now, those who settled the desolate lands of Verse have turned jealous eyes on Earth.
And its riches.
The cradle of all humanity, blessed with water and air in such abundance, that they refract light to make the sea and sky appear blue.
That's not accurate.
Huh?
The blue sky isn't caused by diffraction. It's through the effects of Rayleigh scattering.
What? But Slane said that it was caused by light diffraction.
The sky is blue from Rayleigh scattering, and the clouds are white from me scattering.
Your friend was mistaken.
Uh...
Hmm...
Excuse me. Would it be alright if I took over?
You're a real go-getter, aren't you?
I just want to get a feel for it.
What did you get in docking?
Oh, A-minus, sir. But still...
When we make port, stand next to me and watch.
And get your hands out of your sleeves.
Yes, sir. Sorry, sir. Thank you.
Aren't you guys supposed to give us some uniforms or something?
No, we haven't got enough right now. I'm hoping we can stock up on some at the next port.
That's not too hard on the eyes.
Commander, why would we go to Tanegashima? I thought that area had been sealed off years ago.
With our lack of intel on their Mars landing castles, we want to stay away from likely invasion targets.
Tanegashima was devastated so badly that the very landscape was altered beyond recognition.
There's no longer a civilian population.
That makes sense.
So we're hoping the Martians in Tokyo won't choose it as a viable target.
I never thought I'd come back here.
Isn't it a little early for happy hour?
No, Doc. This drink isn't for me.
It's for the ones I'll never have the chance to again.
John Humoray? Is that who?
Now this...
This one here is for me.
I'm jumping off the wagon.
You want a belt, Doc?
Yeah, maybe I will.
Mind if I join you?
Captain Magburetch.
The Tanegashima report.
I've heard rumors about it, of course.
But I never once believed that it was a fabrication.
And that, Lieutenant Marito...
Is why I have not been able to forgive you.
That battle on Tanegashima...
My big brother fought in it, too.
He was killed in action.
Murdered, rather.
By you.
Magburetch is the name of the family who adopted me.
My birth name was Humoray.
Your best friend was my only brother, John.
What's that?
All anti-air units, get out to sea!
Hard right-runner! Combat speed!
Huh? Me, ma'am?
Give me a damage report.
Missile impact midship. No detonation.
Appears to be a dud. But be careful down there.
What is it?
It's moving. It's alive.
What the hell was that? I need intel.
It's coming back.
Help is not answering. It's going to hit.
All hands. Brace for impact now.
Let's go.
Entering my territory without so much as a by-your-leave?
Oh, this just will not do.
I fear a lesson is needed.
A very harsh one indeed.
What is it doing this far out?
I think this is a different Martian than the one in Tokyo.
Shipboard cataphrats, prepare to launch.
Freezing platoon, launch.
Elevator one, engaged.
Calm. Huh?
It's not powering up.
Sorry. We're running a systems check.
Just give us a minute.
It feels kind of cramped in here.
You know?
Okay. Force feedback checking program starting.
Ejection seat functional.
IFF online.
Tactical data link is activated.
All systems green.
Mustang leader to Mustang 2-2.
Now, you're in a training unit, so you'll be our marksman.
Is that you, Yuki?
But your arm is still...
If my newbie's in the fight,
don't really see how I can sit this one out.
But warrant Officer Kaizuka.
Yuki will be just fine.
Mustang leader, out.
Unbelievable.
Mustang leader, Yuki Kaizuka, commencing launch.
Raising elevator number two, and vehicle elevator.
Frisian platoon, you're on the bow position.
Mustang platoon, deploy to the stern.
All units, intercept airborne enemies.
I almost feel sorry.
Poor inferior race trying to get by without Alt-Noah.
Cower before my might.
Bow down before me.
Then despair and die.
Now fly, my mighty messengers.
Eye unit, you're too close together.
Spread out.
They are tough.
My fists become a giant molecule.
Your bullets can't do a thing.
Mustang leader to all units.
AP rounds are ineffective.
All units switch to high explosives and attack.
Right.
Roger.
Ah, crap.
Lieutenant Marito, where are you going?
I'm playing my home field again.
I am on a team, right?
Or maybe this is an away game.
Hey, Yinko, watch her backs.
Roger that.
Get on your feet.
You're a sitting duck.
Oh, right.
Inaho, I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
This one good?
Oh, Lieutenant Marito.
No, that one's still being tuned.
But it runs okay, right?
I just needed to work for one shot.
Get a heavy barrel ready for it.
Damn it.
Oh, come on.
What's with this?
Block 24 has been breached.
Blocks 23, 24, and 25 taking all water.
Evacuate the affected blocks immediately.
But if we don't seal the bulkheads, we're sure to...
No, it's all right.
The ship is done for anyway.
Abandon ship.
Non-combatants first.
Get the landing craft prepped for launch.
Now what?
This way!
Hurry up!
Please be careful, Your Highness.
Yes, I will.
Enemy units are coming in from above!
Three more!
Closing in from our flanks!
They're using their distance to build up speed!
Their target is the bridge!
I have toyed with you long enough.
Time for you to die!
It's coming!
What was that?
Direct hit!
Next target, three mil right!
Not even HE rounds can get through those things armor plating.
But...
We can use the blast pressure to throw it off course.
Primary craft is still!
Next target, lap seven mil!
Direct hit!
Last target!
We're done!
I'm out of ammo!
Captain!
And now it ends!
What was that?
Huh?
I'm not dead?
That must be a...
End ofbeans.
It won't seem to be a...
Hey...
Like again...
Welcome...
Anyway...
Hey,始まりにも 終わりにも 変わる光
下に向けたまま 飾すの 止めたあの時
LPのサイズの合わない 嘘だかり並べて
見失い 自ら 全てに つまづいた
明日 照らす 8A
繰り返すファウンド 明日の 0時のサイン
ライボタイ 見えない 光の線
持ちだけで 生きる場所 捨てて
名前の見ない外に 答えを戻れてても
風に溶かした 命の霊 投げ捨てない
駆け出しの涙 死体も 闇も アリも
いらない 0になれば 私も Crazy One
原物の感情
ステーサー